(Leonard:)You told her my experiment
was stupid?
(Howard:)I was just repeating
what Sheldon said.
Look, let's not get off topic.
Bernadette, I need to apologize.
You know, I was wrong to tell you
who you should be friends with.
-Should I leave you two alone?
-No, Leonard, you should hear this.
(Leonard:)Okay, good.
Because I wasn't really gonna go.
(Howard:)Look, I know I come off
as confident and worldly...
(Howard:)...but the truth is I'm not.
(Leonard:)We're shocked.
(Howard:)Which is why I tend to feel threatened
by other guys.
(Leonard:)Or loud noises, clowns and nuns.
(Howard:)But I now realize how foolish that is.
(Leonard:)He had a panic attack once
when he got his head stuck in his sweater.
(Howard:)It was a full turtleneck.
-And why aren't you helping me?
-I don't know.
(Leonard:)Maybe because I'm crazy?